Thank you for flying JetBlue.
感谢您乘坐捷蓝航空
Welcome to Las Vegas.
欢迎来到拉斯维加斯
Here you go, here you go.
给你  给你
That was quick.
办得真快
You skip the line when you're on the excelsior level.
尊贵级别客户无需排队
Three rooms adjoing, top floor.
三个房间挨在一起  顶层
Silver, pretty.
银色的  好漂亮
Platinum, so don't wave that around everywhere.
是白金的  所以别拿着到处挥
People'll get jealous.
别人会嫉妒的
Maybe wa it around a little.
或许挥一下也无妨
My friend Burt Tanner runs the hotel.
我朋友伯特・坦纳经营这个酒店
He comped us a few rooms
他免费提供给我们几间房
because we sold him some closets
因为我们卖给他几组橱柜
for his high-roller suites.
安装在他的那些土豪套房里
Zebrawood, heated sock drawer,
斑纹木  可加温的袜子抽屉
the works.
精致做工
Hey, luxury bathroom,
您好  奢华浴室
it's me, lowly closet.
正是在下  卑微的橱柜
Watch your back.
小心点
Mitchell?
米奇尔
Langham?
朗翰姆
Hey, Cam,
小卡
I-it's Langham and Tim!
这是朗翰姆和蒂姆
What are you boys doing here?
你们在这儿干什么
Bachelor-party weekend.
举行我们的告别单身派对
We're getting married in June.
我们要在六月结婚了
What?
什么
Oh, we really wanted to invite you,
我们很想邀请你们的
but Tim's family is huge --
但是蒂姆的家庭成员太多
Relax. We're getting married in May
没事的  我们要在五月结婚
and you're not coming, so...
也没邀请你们  所以
Mitchell.
米奇尔
Oh, look at us moving on.
真好  我们现在都看开了
It's almost like you never dumped me in an e-mail
就像你从未在我跟你说我爱你的
the morning after I told you that I loved you.
第二天早晨用一封邮件把我甩了
Well, y-- in my defense, e-mail --
我得辩解一下  邮件
it was new back then...
在那时候还是新鲜玩意
...and it was still a blurry line
而且还很难说
as to what was appropriate and...
用什么方式是合适的
Well, we have a pretty packed weekend.
我们这周末非常忙
Oh, we do,but if you guys have some time,
没错  如果你们有时间
here's our itinerary.
这是我们的日程表
- Okay.  - Come play.
-好的  -一起来玩吧
- Oh, yeah.  - Fun. Bye.
-没问题  -玩得开心  再见
- You guys, congratulations.   - Thank you.
-恭喜你们  -谢谢
Oh, my gosh,
天啊
an actual gay agenda.
一个真正的同性恋日程
Looks like we're not gonna see much of you two this trip.
看来这些天不会经常看到你们两个了
- No. - No, no.
-不  -不会不会
We are not participating in any of this.
我们是不会参加这上面的任何活动的
They're very judgy about bachelor parties.
他们对于单身派对很挑剔的
I offered to throw them one,
我提出要帮他们办
and I got a whole lecture.
结果被讲了一通大道理
We're 40. We have a child.
我们已经40了  还有个孩子
We've been together for 10 years.
我们已经在一起十年了
That's the one.
又来了
It's just not who we are anymore.
我们已经不是那样的人了
Listen to this -- "Bananas and cabanas pool party."
听听这个  "香蕉小屋泳池派对"
- Oh, Cam.  - Yeah.
-天啊  小卡  -没错
"Most creative speedo
"最具创意泳装获得者
wins tickets to the kilty pleasures."
将赢得苏格兰短裙士兵欢乐秀的门票"
- No!  - Please.
-不要  -得了吧
What is the kilty pleasures?
什么是苏格兰短裙士兵欢乐秀
This.
这个
We will be maintaining our dignity in the spa, thank you.
我们将在水疗室维护我们的尊严  谢谢
I mean, come on,
拜托
have you ever seen a scottish person this tan?
哪有苏格兰人晒到这么黑的
I'm embarrassed even looking at it.
我光看着都觉得难为情
Then stop.
那就别看了
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
■
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译 禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
Whoa, that warmer drawer really works.
那个加温抽屉实在太好使了
It's like my mom's hugging my feet again.
感觉像是我妈又一次抱着我的脚
I'm gonna go do some shopping.
我要去购物了
Oh, well, maybe we'll catch up later.
那我们待会儿再碰头
No, you have your day,
不用了  你忙你的
I'll have mine.
我忙我的
Well, how 'bout the bar at like 5:00?
那五点在酒吧见好吗
Sure.
好的
She was icing me,
她在跟我冷战
but I deserved it.
但是我罪有应得
For the first time in my whole life,
我平生第一次
I was neglecting her.
忽视了她
I'd been invited to audition
我受邀去参加一个
for a secret magic society in Las Vegas,
拉斯维加斯秘密魔法学会的面试
but in all my rehearsals,
但当我没日没夜地彩排时
I'd paid no attention to Claire.
就忽略了克莱尔的存在
I even left her alone in a movie theater once.
我甚至有一次把她单独留在了影院
Oh, no.
大事不妙
I let Phil think I was still mad at him
我让菲尔以为我还在生他的气
because I needed a little time to myself.
因为我需要点私人时间
Come to mama! Yeah!
快到老娘怀里  太棒了
Years ago, Phil and I put aside money
几年前  菲尔和我攒了些钱
for a trip on our 25th anniversary,
为了在结婚25年纪念日出去旅行
but I lost that money on
但有个周末我和女朋友们
a girls' weekend in vegas.
去赌城把钱输光了
Since then, I've been on a secret mission
从那时起  我就在执行一个秘密任务
to win that money back,
为了把钱赢回来
and if things go well this weekend,
如果这周末一切顺利的话
I am even.
我就能回本了
Vegas, you have a gambling problem,
拉斯维加斯  你有个赌博问题
and her name is Claire.
她的名字就叫克莱尔
Knockity-knock-knock.
咚咚咚
Mr. Dunphy, I presume?
我猜您是邓菲先生吧
Yes. Who-- hi.
是的  你好
I'm Leslie Higgins
我叫莱斯利・希金斯
it's a boy's name where I'm from.
在我家乡这是个男孩名
I'm your butler.
我是您的管家
Oh. Butler. Cool.
管家啊  真好
Yes. As an excelsior guest,
是的  作为尊贵客人
uh, I'm at your beck and call 24/7.
我24小时随时待命为您服务
Anything you need, big or small, I can
任何事情  大事小情  我都能
Can I just segue, sir,
先生  我能不能接下来
to the importance of discretion in my job?
向您介绍我会如何保护您的隐私
I'll just pop those --
我就把这些放在...
Oh, no, no, no. Never mind those.
不不不  不用管了
- As you wish.   - They're for an appointment I have later.
- 如您所愿   - 我等下有个约会要用到它
The less you know about that, the better.
你知道的越少越好
A myriad of apologies, sir.
实在非常抱歉  先生
If there's nothing else...
如果没有别的事...
Oh, hang on.
等下
Actually, do you know where I can get a cape laundered?
你知道哪儿能洗披肩吗
Opera or superhero?
歌剧还是那种超级英雄披肩
I'd rather not say.
不便透露
I overstepped the mark by asking.
这个问题越线了
Uh, could I just, uh, quickly point out
我能不能小小地介绍下
our luxury bath service, sir?
我们的豪华沐浴服务  先生
We have five outrageously decadent baths
我们提供五种超级豪华沐浴套餐
that I can prepare for you at a moment's notice.
您若需要我马上就能为您准备好
Uh, I should just point out, though,
不过需要说明的是
that our Pharaoh's Fantasy does take a dash longer,
"法老的幻想"套餐需要花费一点时间
normally, because our Nubian lives off-site.
因为我们的努比亚人演员不常驻酒店
Um...if there's nothing else,
如果没有别的吩咐
I'll just help you with your case.
我就帮您把箱子放好
Uh, no, uh --
不
- I'll get that.  - Yeah.
-我自己来吧  -好的
All right. Thank you.
好了  谢谢
- I love cucumber water.  - I know.
-我爱死黄瓜水了  -我知道
- If I were president   - I know, I know.
-如果我是总统  -我知道我知道
Cucumbers in the reservoirs.
就在水库里装满黄瓜
Giant cucumbers.
巨大的黄瓜
Mr. Pritchett?
普里契特先生
Yes, hi.
是的
All right, I'll see you in 90 minutes.
好了  90分钟后见
- Enjoy.   - Thank you.
-好好享受  -谢谢
Mr. Tucker?
塔克先生
We had a few no-shows for the Britney concert, so...
有几位客人决定不去布兰妮的演唱会了
One, please.
我要一张  谢谢
Uh, what about Mitchell?
那米奇尔呢
It's Vegas -- he doesn't need to know what I'm doing.
这里是赌城  他不需要知道我在做什么
I don't need to know what he's doing.
我也不需要知道他在做什么
So if you see him,
所以如果你见到他
maybe don't mention what I'm doing.
也别告诉他我在做什么
Oh. Understood.
了解
So, do you have anything on the aisle?
你有挨着走廊的座位吗
Yeah?
哪位
Rasputin's Dalmatian drowned in the Volga.
拉斯普京的达马西亚人淹死在伏尔加河
I thought he was allergic to dogs.
我以为他对狗过敏
You're thinking of Merlin.
你想的是梅林
And it was peanuts.
应该是花生
Okay, everybody.
大家好
We have a visitor.
我们来了个客人
Welcome Phil Dunphy.
欢迎菲尔・邓菲
Hey, Phil.
你好  菲尔
Hey. I'm so honored to be here.
你好  能来到这儿很荣幸
You may recognize my -- my screen name,
你们也许认识我的用户名
Abracadunphy17.
天灵地灵邓菲17
That's you?
那是你吗
You're up in the middle of the night a lot.
你经常在半夜上线
My wife grinds her teeth.
我太太睡觉磨牙
But let me tell you another story.
但让我给你们讲另一个故事吧
It's about the miracle of metamorphosis.
是关于变形奇迹的
- Uh, Phil   - They say the only constant is change --
-菲尔  -人们说唯一不变的是变化
Phil, we're gonna get to your trick in just a minute.
菲尔  我们等下再看你的表演
Oh. I'm sorry.
不好意思
Got a little excited there.
有点小激动了
The heroes of the underground-magic blogosphere --
博客界地下魔术师中的英雄们
"Flashpaper" Finelli, Kaiser Mayhem, the Kid.
"闪火纸"菲内利  凯撒杀手  小孩
When you think about it,
想想看
it's crazy they're all alive at the same time.
能同时见到活生生的他们简直不可思议
Jay, I'm feeling a little cold.
杰  我觉得有点冷
Maybe I should buy a scarf.
也许我该买条围巾
Sure, get a couple of 'em.
当然  买两条
Why, I know it's a little extravagant,
怎么  我知道这有点奢侈
but we're excelsior now --
但我们现在是尊贵客人了
might as well look it.
当然要有尊贵的样子
Many years ago, when Jay was in Las Vegas,
很多年前  杰在拉斯维杰斯时
he bought Barkley,
买了巴克利
the doggy butler.
那个狗管家
I hate Barkley.
我恨死巴克利了
I knew if Jay saw Rebarka,
我知道如果杰看到丽巴卡
he would want her too.
他也会想买的
Yeah, that's her name -- Rebarka.
是的  那是她的名字  丽巴卡
Uh, but, uh -- you know,
但是  那个
if we're going to gamble,
如果我们要去赌博
maybe I need my lucky sweater.
也许我需要那件幸运毛衣
Can you go and get it in the room?
你能去房间里帮我拿来吗
Who has a lucky sweater?
你怎么还有幸运毛衣
You wore two different shoes to watch the Super Bowl.
你看超级杯赛时还穿两只不一样的鞋呢
Fine.
好吧
No, Jay!
别  杰
Other way.
走那边
I like that way.
我喜欢那边
Sorry, sir. This is a private elevator.
不好意思先生  这是私人电梯
No need to apologize.
不用道歉
I'm glad you're on top of this stuff.
我很高兴你业务熟练
That's only for the excelsior level.
您的卡只能到达尊贵客户层
This elevator goes to the top floor.
这架电梯是去顶层的
I thought excelsior was the top -- 62.
我以为尊贵级别就是顶层  62层
Mandalay Bay has 63 floors.
曼德勒海湾酒店有63层
Top floor is excelsior plus.
顶层是高级尊贵层
Wait, they're allowed up there?
等等  他们可以上去吗
They're wearing dungarees.
他们穿的是粗布工作服啊
61, 62...63!
[曼德勒海湾酒店]
Son of a bitch!
你妹
Come on, let me see an eight.
拜托  给我来个八
I want to see an eight.
我想要个八
Seven out.
七
Sorry.
抱歉
We'll get 'em next time, baby.
我们下把会赢的  宝贝
Claire. Give me your key.
克莱尔  把你的钥匙给我
I need to charge something to your room.
我有个东西得记在你房间的账上
Hang on a second.
等一下
Four. Point is four.
四  点数是四
Okay, odds on four and a five each on "C" And "E."
好的  赌四和五在C和E上
What are you talking about?
你刚才说什么
It's the lady version of Barkley.
是巴克利的女款
I have to put it on hold
我得预订上
so that Jay, if he sees it, he can't buy it,
这样杰就算看到也买不到了
and then I will cancel the charge before we leave.
然后走时我会把帐销掉的
Winner-- four the hard way!
赢家是  四  真不易
Oh, yes! Finally!
太棒了  终于押上了
Can I have the key?
能给我钥匙吗
Oh, no, honey. You're not going anywhere.
不  亲爱的  你哪都别去
You're my good-luck charm.
你是我的幸运女神
Give these a blow, beautiful.
吹口气  美女
And how was your massage?
按摩得怎么样
So re--
太放
So, so relaxing.
太放松了
Sorry, my masseuse was blasting the Enya.
抱歉我的按摩师一直在放恩雅的音乐
So, what are you gonna do next?
你接下来想干点什么呢
A long soak?
泡个澡
A long sauna?
还是蒸个桑拿
I think a sauna.
我想蒸桑拿
Yeah, I think I'm gonna do a soak.
是吗  我想泡个澡
Ooh, a soak does sound nice.
泡澡也不错
Maybe I'll do a sauna.
要不我还是蒸桑拿吧
Is that-- is that glitter on your face?
你脸上那是亮粉吗
Yeah, I think my masseuse might moonlight.
是啊  我的按摩师可能夜间兼职
Vegas.
拉斯维加斯嘛
- All right, I'll see you in an hour.  - Okay. Yeah.
-好吧  一小时后见  -好的
Enjoy it. Really have fun.
好好享受吧
Relax, Mitchell.
放松  米奇尔
Phil, you're up.
菲尔  该你了
Okay.
好的
The miracle... of metamorphosis.
化茧成蝶的奇迹
They say the only constant is change.
人们说唯一不变的是变化
Well, all of that is about to ch-- be different.
然而一切都将变  不同
Note the simple burlap sack,
注意这只是个粗麻袋
the kind you'd find in any home.
家里随意都能找到
If you'd be so kind as to assist me,
可以麻烦你帮我一下吗
the-- the-- the Kid,
孩子
I'll endeavor to prove that some change is glacial,
我要尽力证明一些变化是漫长的
while some change is instantaneous.
而有一些变化是瞬间的
Now, if you'd be so kind as to raise the simple burlap sack
现在麻烦你把粗麻袋提起来
above my head and pinch my wrists.
提过我的头  在我手腕处收紧
You'll note, the clock says exactly 4:02.
注意时间是4点02分
I have 3:15.
我的表是3点15
Yeah, I have 6:35.
我的是6点35
Kaiser Mayhem!
凯撒杀手
It's what I do.
是我干的
Wait, it's 5:20?
等等  已经5点20了吗
I actually have to call my wife.
我得给我太太打个电话
Oh, no, Phil, you can't just stop in the middle of a trick.
不行  菲尔  不能在魔术半途停下来
That's a cardinal rule.
这是基本的行规
Guys, it's an emergency.
各位  这是紧急情况
Don't tell me you've never
别跟我说你们从未
had to call your spouse.
不得不停下来打给另一半
Oh...there's-- there's people for you.
你们  你们会找到另一半的
Come on, Claire. Please pick up.
拜托  克莱尔  快接啊
And the lady wins again.
又是这位女士赢了
Yes! Yes!
很好  很好
I did it! I did it!
我做到了  我做到了
I did it! I won back my money.
我做到了  我赢回了我的钱
Oh, suck it, the house.
认输吧  豪斯
Claire, the key.
克莱尔  钥匙
Yeah, okay, here you go.
好的  好的  给你
And, hey, buy yourself something sparkly.
给自己买点闪闪的东西吧
Gloria, there's a floor above us.
歌洛莉亚  我们上面还有一层
- What?!   - I know. It threw me, too.
-什么  -是啊  我也很震惊
Excelsior plus.
高级尊贵层
But to the people on that floor,
但对于那层的人来说
we're excelsior minus.
我们就是次级豪华
Mm, what is up there?
那上面有什么呢
You need a black card to get in.
得拿黑卡才能进入
All we've got is this stupid silver one.
可我们只有这破烂银卡
Oh, I thought it was platinum.
我还以为是铂金卡呢
It's crap.
这是垃圾
Uh, why-
为什么
why don't you call your friend Burt
你何不打给你的朋友伯特
and tell him that we need the black card?
跟他说我们需要黑卡呢
Because he's not my friend.
因为他不是我的朋友
I never really even met him.
我都没见过他
I think I heard him cough one time on a conference call.
我可能就在一次电话会议上听到过他咳嗽
I don't know why he would treat me this way.
不知道他为什么要这么对我
- Oh, come on!   - What?
-不是吧  -怎么了
Oh, come on! You're Jay Pritchett!
不是吧  你是杰・普里契特
You're gonna find your friend Burt
你要找到你的朋友伯特
and tell him who you are,
告诉他你是谁
and you're gonna get the black card,
你会要到黑卡
because when you set your mind on something,
因为当你决定做一件事
nobody can stop you!
没人能阻止你
Right!
没错
Wait!
等等
Go that way.
从那边走
Excuse me,
不好意思
how much is that doggy in the window?
橱窗里那只狗多少钱
I had finally taken back from Vegas what Vegas took from me.
我终于从赌城手里拿回了属于我的东西
That's a feeling of satisfaction I can't describe...
那种满足感很难形容
Because it didn't last very long.
因为没持续太久
- Oh, hey, Claire.  - Yeah?
-克莱尔  -什么事
- Have you seen Cam?  - No.
-你看到小卡了吗  -没有
Although...we should stay in one place so he can find us.
我们应该呆在一个地方好让他找到我们
How about a blackjack table?
找个二十一点牌桌怎么样
Oh, no, I'm really worn out from my massage, the sauna...
不  我刚做完按摩和桑拿  很困
It was just-- it was a lot of detoxing.
排出了很多毒素
You know what you need?
知道你需要什么吗
- Some toxing.  - No.
-来点毒素  -不
Hand of blackjack, couple of tequilas.
玩几盘二十一点  再喝几杯龙舌兰
Come on, it'll be fun. Do it.
来嘛  可好玩了  快去
You sound just like the kid who bullied me
你听起来就像小时候
into smoking my first cigarette.
逼我抽第一支烟那个人
Maybe this time you won't tell on me.
也许这次你不会告发我
- And then hit.  - Yes.
-继续拿牌  -好
And then hit. And then stay.
继续拿牌  然后停牌
- I know. I have it.   - Okay.
-我知道怎么玩  -好吧
18, 19, 18.
十八点  十九点  十八点
You are in a great position right now.
你赢面很大
Oh, the dealer has 21.
庄家是二十一点
Hers is better.
她的牌更好
I am so sorry, Mitchell.
真不好意思  米奇尔
I promise you, we did everything right.
可我保证我们刚刚每一步都做对了
Don't be mad.
别太不爽
- I'm not mad.  - Really?
-我没有不爽  -真的吗
T-that was -- that was thrilling. I'm...
我只是  只是太激动了
- My pulse is racing.  - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
-我心跳加快了  -是吧  好玩吧
- Thank you so much for making me do this.   - Yeah.
-真谢谢你让我玩这个  -那当然
I'm going to play another hand.
我要再玩一局
We're going to play another hand.
我们要再玩一局
No, alone.
不是我们  是我
- Not with you. You're bad luck.   - Really?
-我不带你玩  霉运走开  -真的吗
Go -- far.
走远一点
The minute I got rid of her,
我一摆脱她
I couldn't lose.
就开始一路狂赢
Oh, gambling's fun.
赌钱真好玩
And easy.
还很简单
Hey, big spender.
你好  土豪哥
What are you doing?
你在干什么呢
Gambling. I'm a gambler now.
赌博  我现在是个赌徒
- Look at you, letting loose.   - Yeah.
-本性暴露了啊  -没错
Yeah, I guess I figure
我想通了
whatever mischief one might get into in Vegas
不管在赌城玩得多疯
kind of remains here within the limits of the city, you know?
出了赌城就都不存在了
- That's a cool way to think about it.  - Yeah.
-这想法很酷  -是吧
You know, I'm really glad that you came over here.
我真的很高兴在这里碰到你
Really? Why is that?
真的吗  为什么
Well, I always hated the way
我一直很遗憾
that things ended between us, you know?
我们当年结束得不太愉快
Maybe now we can go out on a better note.
说不定我们现在可以尝试好好相处
- That's nice.   - Yeah.
-那样很好  -没错
Oh -- oh, my god!
天啊
6-2-3-3, that's -- that's my room number.
6-2-3-3  这是我的房号
Huh. Um, hit me.
要牌
Seven!
七
That's 21, huh?
是二十一点
Yes! Yeah! Ah!
太棒了
Whoa, check you out.
瞧瞧  你真厉害
I guess tonight's my night to get lucky.
我觉得今晚是我的幸运之夜
I would say.
我也觉得
- Here you are. - Thank you.
-给你  -谢谢
- Maybe I will run into you again, huh?   - Okay.
-我们说不定很快就会再见面  -好
Oh, you...
那个  你
There are $2140, Higgins,
这里有2140美金  希金斯
for nothing -- nothing!
天降横财  天降横财
I want to do something crazy.
我要做点疯狂的事
Okay, I'm gonna order a bath.
我要订一个沐浴套餐
Sir, it seems to me like you've gone mad.
先生  我觉得您好像癫狂了
Okay, this is what I want.
要的就是这个效果
I want something romantic,
我想来点浪漫
but also a little dangerous.
但又带点危险的
Romantic, dangerous --
浪漫又危险
might I suggest, sir, the techno bath?
如果让我建议的话  电子乐沐浴怎么样
Your heart will throb with the bass
您的心脏将和贝司一起脉动
while your eyes take in an off-the-scale laser light show
您的双眼将享受一场超高端激光秀
from that most intimate of V.I.P. arenas
一切都在最私密的贵宾场所进行
-- your own tub.
也就是您自己的浴缸
Okay. I want that.
好  就要那个了
That's what I want.
正是我想要的
Me thinks the little red riding hood may be a big, bad wolf.
我觉着小红帽实际上是只大坏狼
I'll be back shortly with supplies.
我很快就带着需要的东西回来
Okay!
好
Ah, Mr. Dunphy! How are...
邓菲先生  今晚
...we this evening?
过得怎么样
Not so good.
不怎么样
I'm in a tight spot with my lady.
跟我老婆起了点摩擦
You know what might help?
你知道什么能有所帮助吗
One of those -- one of those luxury baths.
不如来一个那种  豪华沐浴套餐
Ah, get yourself out of some hot water
将她置于温暖的泡澡水当中
by getting her into some.
以解救自己于水深火热之中
Wow, so good.
太棒了
Might I suggest the Michael Buble Bath?
我的建议是麦可・布雷泡泡浴
You are a mind reader.
你简直会读心术
I'm not a mind reader, sir.
我不会读心术  先生
I've just been in the bath-buttling business
我只是从九十年代起
since the early '90s,
就干沐浴管家这行了
despite my fresh face.
尽管我看起来很年轻
So I tend to know what these situations need.
所以我很了解什么情况选什么套餐
- I'll get the water going. - As you wish.
-我这就去放水  -如您所愿
Same price either way.
反正价格都一样
Burt says he's gonna be here any minute.
伯特说他马上就过来
We got to really lay it on for this guy --
我们一定要好好招待他
best scotch, put on something sexy.
最好的苏格兰威士忌  穿得性感点
I... have a great idea!
我  我有个好主意
Cigars!
雪茄
A man like Burt appreciates a good cigar.
伯特那种男人一定会喜欢上好的雪茄
Good thinking!
这主意不错
Of course, upstairs, the butler would be here already.
当然要是在楼上  管家早就来了
I'm telling you,
我告诉你吧
we might as well be sleeping in the basement.
我们这就跟睡在地下室一样
I said hold it, not deliver it!
我说的是"存"货不是"送"货
Okay, there.
好吧  这边
Come here.
过来这里
Stay in Claire's room.
好好待在克莱尔的屋子里
Hey, honey. I'm in the bathroom.
亲爱的  我在浴室里呢
Honey?
亲爱的
Okay, I-I know I messed up,
好吧  我知道我错了
But sit tight -- I got a little surprise for you.
但坐好  我为你准备了惊喜
Higgins, you got a minute?
希金斯  你有空吗
60 an hour.
一小时里有60分钟有空
They all belong to you, sir.
全都由您支配  先生
I need a couple of primo cigars, A.S.A.P.
我需要尽快搞一些高级雪茄
I'm not a stickler for how they got in the country.
我不在乎它们是如何到达我们国家的
I'm also expecting a special Scotch delivery.
我还在等一瓶特制苏格兰威士忌
I need a shave.
还需要刮个胡子
Burt can't see me like this.
我不能这样去见伯特
Unfortunately, the shaving butlers are all --
很遗憾  剃须管家只在
I know, excelsior plus.
我知道  只有高级尊贵层有
- Are you decent?   - I am.
-方便进来吗  -方便
Well, not for long.
很快就不方便了哦
My partner should be here any minute.
我的爱人随时就要回来了
Is it me, sir,
先生  是我的原因吗
or is the air positively fizzing with erotic anticipation?
还是这空气中本就充满了情爱的氛围
Yeah.
是啊
Oh, I forgot the ice.
我忘了拿冰块
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna get it.
我这就去拿
Oh, I couldn't ask you to do that.
怎么能让您去呢
No, not a problem.
不  没关系的
As you wish.
那好吧
Same price either way.
反正都是一样的价格
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
不好意思
I-I'm looking for Mitchell.
我想找米奇尔
Oh, yeah, he's expecting you.
是的  他正在等您
In fact, he's asked me to draw the two of you a bath.
事实上  他让我帮两位准备了沐浴
- This is crazy.   - Yeah.
-太疯狂了  -是啊
I believe that's the plan.
我觉得这正是他的本意
Enjoy.
请尽情享受
Thank you.
谢谢
Oh, good. You're back.
太好了  你回来了
How's Claire seem?
克莱尔看起来心情如何
I'm sorry?
什么
You must have seen her out there. Is she mad?
你在外面肯定碰到她了吧  她生气了吗
W-what's she doing?
她在干什么
Uh, she's dusting, sir.
她在除尘  先生
Oh, she always cleans when she's mad.
她生气时总是喜欢打扫
Do me a favor --
帮我个忙
Bring her a drink
给她拿杯饮料
and tell her to get comfortable on the couch.
让她在沙发上休息一下
She's -- she's allowed on the furniture, is she?
她可以趴上家具是吧
She's my wife.
她是我妻子
Oh, good! I've been looking for you.
太好了  我正在找你
Well, you should have been looking for somebody
你应该正在找一个
who was looking for you,
正在找你的人
because that's what I was doing.
因为那正是我在做的事
Come on, I have a surprise for you.
快来  我给你准备了惊喜
Yeah, I-I've been thinking
是啊  我一直在想
we need to stop being so uptight.
我们不能总是这么紧张又保守
We are in Vegas.
我们可是在赌城啊
Let's have a little fun.
我们来找点乐子吧
Well, I'll have to wrap my head around that, but okay.
我得努力适应一下  但好吧
Now, I have just the way to kick it off --
我正好知道要如何开始
something we could do together.
这件事我们可以一起做
It's a little extreme,
虽然尺度有点大
- but I think it might be just what we need.   - Okay.
-但我觉得那正是我们需要的  -好吧
Go on in.
继续往里走
Are you crazy?
你疯了吗
Oh, come on, Cam, we deserve this.
行了  小卡  我们应该放松一下
All right, you get started,
好了  你先进去
and then I'll jump in when it starts to heat up.
热一下身  我马上就来
Mitchell!
米奇尔
Come on. Then I will throw you into it, tiger.
快来  不然我要把你扔进去了
Rub a dub dub.
来嘛来嘛
Dear, no.
天哪  不
Langham.
朗翰姆
Both of you?
你们两个都来吗
Huh. Well, okay.
那好吧
No. No. No, not okay.
不  不  不  不好
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么
You gave me your room key.
你把房卡给我了
What?!
什么
Don't act so shocked.
别装的这么吃惊
You told me at the bachelor party
你在单身派对的时候跟我说
you two lead separate lives.
你们两个有各自的生活
You went to the bachelor party?
你去单身派对了
Yes, and I was starting to feel bad about sneaking around,
是的  然后我开始为自己的行为内疚
but I guess I shouldn't have,
但现在看来是我多虑了
Now that I see what you're up to.
现在我明白你有什么打算了
I'm not up to anything!
我什么打算也没有
I left my key by mistake.
我是不小心遗落了房卡
We're all obviously tense.
我们显然都很焦躁
Let's take a deep breath...
让我们都深呼吸一下
Get in the tub...
进来浴缸里
That's not happening.
没可能的
You want to tell me
你想跟我说一下
how you "Accidentally" gave someone your key?
你是如何"不小心"把房卡给了别人吗
You want to tell me why you spent all day
那你想跟我说一下你一整天是如何
sipping tequila out of some guy's navel?
从某个男人的肚脐上喝龙舌兰酒的吗
You saw that?
你看见了
I guessed.
我猜的
Hi, guys. What's going on?
伙计们  出了什么事
Hey, Claire. Can you please just come back?
克莱尔  你能等下再来吗
We're in the middle of an argument.
我们正在吵架
Oh. Bet I know why.
我猜我知道原因
Are you guys getting in the bath?
你们还要进来泡澡吗
Or I'm way off.
也许我猜错了
Langham!
朗翰姆
It's Tim.He can't know I'm here.
是蒂姆  不能让他知道我在这
He has insane trust issues.
他有非常严重的信任问题
Insane?
非常严重
Langham, are you in there?
朗翰姆  你在里面吗
- Go out this door.  - In here.
-从这个门出去  -在这里
Gloria, hurry up, will you?
歌洛莉亚  快点好吗
He's on his way up.
他就要上来了
I need to shave.
我要刮胡子
Oh, you're here.
你来啦
Jay Pritchett.
我是杰・普里契特
Thanks for stopping by.
谢谢你过来
Nice robe.
浴袍不错
Like Hef, Back In The Day.
像《重回昨日》里那个何夫
I'm gonna cut to the chase.
我就有话直说了
I like your lifestyle.
我喜欢你的生活方式
I want a taste of it.
我也想感受一下
Well, s-sure, that's flattering, but...
当然  我很荣幸  但是
Okay, the bathroom is all you--
好吧  浴室是你的了
Gloria, it's Burt Tanner!
歌洛莉亚  这位是伯特・坦纳
That's not Burt Tanner,
那才不是伯特・坦纳
that's Long-ham.
那是朗翰姆
Langham!
朗翰姆
What's that thing doing here?
那玩意在这里干什么
Just enjoying a dirty martini
享用一杯马天尼酒
before a cleansing romp in the bath.
只为在那浴室中荡涤嬉闹
That's not who the bath is for.
我不是为这位准备的沐浴
Oh, my mistake.
我搞错了
Welcome...Claire.
欢迎您  克莱尔
You're certainly gonna be clean
过了今晚
by the end of the night, aren't you?
你一定会洁净如初的  不是吗
Jay, I forgot all my hair products!
杰  我的护发品都忘带了
I'm going to borrow from Claire.
我去和克莱尔借一下
Okay, the coast is clear.
好  安全了
Jay!
杰
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
快走  快快快
Hey. Phil, there you are.
菲尔  你在这里啊
Ducky! How'd you know where I was?
德奇  你怎么知道我在哪里
Magicians run this town.
这座城市由魔法师掌管
Really?
真的吗
No. I'm a shaving butler up on plus.
才不是  我是高级尊贵层的修面管家
Look, I felt bad about how things went down today,
今天发生的事情让我感到很抱歉
and I-I just wanted to give you another shot.
所以我想过来再给你一次机会
Right this way.
这边请
I really think you're gonna like what you see.
我真的觉得你会喜欢我的表演
Okay, let me just get everything set up.
先让我布置一下
Metamorphosis.
破茧成蝶
They say the only constant is change.
人们说唯一不变的是变化
I-I'm sorry, what -- I-- s-- what is that?
不好意思  那个是啥
Oh, I don't even know.
我也不知道
Something my wife bought.
可能是我老婆买的东西
Let me just get rid of it. Here we go.
我来把它拿走  开始
Really, uh, rubbing it in on that wife thing, huh?
不是吧  又触动人家没有老婆的痛处
Metamorphosis.
破茧成蝶
Burt!
伯特
Nice of you to come down a floor
非常高兴你能从楼上降阶相见
and see how the other half lives.
来看看底层人民是怎么生活的
If you will,
如果你愿意
raise it above my head and pinch it at my wrists.
请帮我把它提过头顶  在我手腕处收紧
Go ahead and make it good and tight.
只管系紧扎好
Don't be easy on me.
不用给我放水
Okay.
好了
Now...
现在
as the lowly caterpillar becomes the majestic butterfly,
就像小小的橡树子成长为参天大树那样
as the tiny acorn becomes the mighty oak,
卑微的毛毛虫变成了壮丽的蝴蝶
so, too, do we complete our...
于是  我们完成了
metamorphosis.
破茧成蝶
So, it's the Governor's Bluff.
所以这只是虚张声势的把戏而已
Well, it's a huge twist on the Governor's Bluff.
不  这可是对虚张声势的极大改善
No, no, no, no, no!
不不不
There were other elements.
这里还有其他的元素
You just kind of threw me off.
你把我弄慌了
I forgot -- I was gonna --
我都忘了  我本应该
as a flourish I was gonna use one --
华丽丽地出场  我应该用一个
A-- that's amazing!
太赞了
Y-you lull me with this--
你用这种
- with this hacky quick change,
快捷变装迷惑我
and the whole time,
与此同时
you're changing the fake dog into a hot maid?
却把一只狗模型变成了火辣女佣
It's brilliant! It's magic!
太有才了  这才是魔术
No, that's metamorphosis!
不  那叫做破茧成蝶
Like you, Burt,
和你一样  伯特
I enjoy the finer things.
我享受更上乘的东西
As a matter of fact,
事实上
that's probably the Cuban I ordered for you.
那可能是我为你定的古巴货到了
Cam, if you wanted a bachelor party,
小卡  要是你想要一场单身派对
you should have just said something.
你早说就好了嘛
Well, I didn't know I wanted one until we got here.
我是在到这里以后  才知道我想要的
And you're so "Eh, eh, eh,"
可你却一直这样叹气
- I-I was afraid to say anything.   - Okay, all right.
-我都不敢说什么  -好吧
Lucky for the two of you,
对于你们俩  幸运的是
I know you better than you know yourselves,
我比你们自己更了解你们
and what the two of you need
而你俩所需要的是一点点
is a little guilty pleasure,
具有罪恶感的小乐趣
or should I say...
或者我可以称之为...
The Scotch delivery you had me on the lookout for, sir.
先生  您让我留意的苏格兰快递到了
I like your style, Pritchett.
我喜欢你的作风  普里契特
You're in.
你入围了
Vegas.
维加斯
This reminds me of my late grandfather.
这让我想起了我过世的爷爷
He was Scottish?
他是苏格兰人吗
He was a stripper.
他是脱衣舞男
There we go.
好了
You've got the touch, kid.
孩子  你手艺不错
I was blessed with my mother's small hands, sir.
我有幸继承了我母亲的小手  先生
Shall I order your complimentary,
我可以为您点一个免费赠送的
in-room, hot-stone massage?
室内魔石按摩吗
Complimentary?
免费赠送的吗
All part of the excelsior-plus experience, sir.
全都属于您高级贵宾体验之内的  先生
Might be nice after a dip in your private lap pool.
您先在私人健身泳池中泡一会儿再做更好
Oh, where has this been all my life?
我从前怎么都没享受过这个
You know, I saw a harpist in the elevator.
我在电梯里看到一个竖琴师
Can we get that for our brunch tomorrow?
我们明天早午餐时可以让他过来演奏么
If it was up to me, yes, but unfortunately,
要是我说了算肯定行  但是很遗憾
that is reserved for our excelsior-ultra guests only.
那是我们尊享极致会员的专属项目
62, 63, 64!
62  63  64层
Son of a bitch!
你妹